ratedesi.com 2010-12-29

# Rate Desi - The Desi HOT or NOT site

**User Information**

All users who register for an account at RateDesi.com retain anonymity if desired. However, the nature of the website is for users to interact with other users. So, once a user participates at RateDesi.com, his/her information may be shared. 

However, user's email addresses are never given to other users or organizations. The other information is displayed in a public member profile. A user may sign up for the site without posting his/her picture. 

**The Cookie Principle**

RateDesi.com may use cookies to improve your web browsing experience. A cookie keeps you logged into the website. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that use if you desire. 

**Information Collected**

Your user actions at the website are not anonymous. We do collect and track your: 

date/time of your visit,  
your IP address,  
the URL of sites you visit, 

We can also match an IP address to any comment or private message you send. 

**Disclosure**

RateDesi.com openly volunteers its practices of collecting information, its targeting capabilities, and its use of cookies. If you have any questions pertaining to this privacy policy and its contents, please direct your correspondence to admin@ratedesi.com. 

**Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information**

If a user�s personally identifiable information changes, or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users� personally identifiable information. This can be done by logging into your user account and updating your personal information or discontinuing service at anytime. 

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with an appropriate law enforcement investigation, current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Ad servers or Web site. 

**Third Party Advertising**

We use BUDS INC, MaxWorldwide and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click here <<http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp>>

**Third Party Cookies**

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. 

**Notification of Changes**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post these changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Regardless of later updates, we will never use the information you submit under this current policy in a new way without first providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prevent that use.
